<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://front.the42.info/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://front.the42.info/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-02-10T22:02:32+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/feed.xml</id><title type="html">the42Front</title><subtitle>Rebuilds after rebuilds. This time modernize.</subtitle><author><name>the42game</name></author><entry><title type="html">It’s no longer funny as joke rn, yet another cycle just dropped.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/10/yet-another-cycle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s no longer funny as joke rn, yet another cycle just dropped." /><published>2026-02-10T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-02-10T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/02/10/yet-another-cycle</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/10/yet-another-cycle.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="not-much-really-to-say">Not much really to say.</h2>
<p>Just go check last post.</p>

<h2 id="now-i-feel-i-gotta-make-lemon-republic-great-again">Now I feel I gotta make Lemon Republic great again.</h2>
<p>No it’s real.<br />
Meet Lemon Republic’s Yuri Specialist, the one and only the42game is back.<br />
Someone which less than 20hrs was looking for the place to hang themselves.<br />
Now is messing around with <a href="https://ja.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E7%99%BE%E5%90%88_(%E3%82%B8%E3%83%A3%E3%83%B3%E3%83%AB)#%E7%94%A8%E8%AA%9E">Yuri Comics and Novels and Anime</a> and actual Japanese Lesbian Drama, omg.<br />
See that’s how fucking crazy Bipolar is, when you enter Manic mode, the globe is on your hand not to mention this person takes <em>Concerta</em> today so even more crazy that they have decided to mess around with their second Intel Arc B580 and found out <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wintel#Modern_situation">Wintel</a> is still true even to this day when the driver/software api supports for Windows is 10x better than that Intel provided for Linux.</p>

<h2 id="will-never-run-llamacpp-with-sycl-on-linux-again">Will never run llama.cpp with SYCL on Linux again.</h2>
<p>Don’t trust me? Run llama.cpp with SYCL on Arch Linux to see for yourself. On Windows it only took 5 mins to set up here I looked for which one is the actual guide to use for Linux that doesn’t shout telemetry to your face yes I am talking about you Ubuntu took me like 2hrs building it took another 1hr, why don’t I just go and buy a Beefy Mac at this point? No offense but I could actually go and buy a 32GB fully loaded M4 Mac mini back home from an Apple Store in less than 1hr no joke.</p>

<p>Be fair the whole setup is poorman’s gaming rig for someone who don’t actually game, R5-3600 factory clock speed with 32GB DDR4 Memory plus Intel Arc B580 in 2026? “Hah!” they laughed in 2025, they stopped laughing in late 2025, and now they’re <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pluribus_(TV_series)">joining(no not that joining in pluribus thats wayyy too crazy for me and I stand with Carol on that, and I just hope ppl won’t download a random executable from whatever alien from space and run it, Vince could see the future)</a>.</p>

<h2 id="wrapping-up">Wrapping up?</h2>

<p>So the thing is now I am going to take some pain killlers and some lithiums, and thinking about what I should read next, I might wake up and watch some <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haibane_Renmei"><em>Haibane Renmei</em></a>, and maybe do sth else but for now I am going to do sth else, at least I could hangin there for a little bit longer, suicide plan recalled, you won.</p>

<p>So anyway, did ya all see that? Normies? Non-believers? Doctors who really want to look into this(Thank you!)? this is how fucking crazy Bipolar is on my body to a point that even I fricking knew it was happening.  I was about to kill myself last night, and lithiums doesn’t do much, anime did nothing, yuri manga basically nothing, but once switching mode, you got your life on your hand again, just that you are stuck in a loop and you have no idea how painful you would be and the only thing you could do now is to prevent being super hype when in Manic so that when Depressive hits you won’t get yourself killed that fast.</p>

<p>And thank again to those who are still backing me up in this tough spicy situation and standing firmly on my back, and those doctor who actually pays attention to patients feelings.</p>

<p>See ya, gosh I must have watched it some where long time ago… I mean <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haibane_Renmei"><em>Haibane Renmei</em></a>, It feels like something I would watch back when my home still got that large Sony Trinitron CRT with a DVD Player(aka when I was a kid). And I had tons of deja vu moments when watching… idk. Oh yeah the last few part is for my/my docs future reference.<br />
Ughh I am really going to talk Lithiums now…</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not funny anymore fuck I really got bipolar-2.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I should’ve put an end to this long before the outbreak.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/09/live-for-no-reason-is-boring.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I should’ve put an end to this long before the outbreak." /><published>2026-02-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-02-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/02/09/live-for-no-reason-is-boring</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/09/live-for-no-reason-is-boring.html"><![CDATA[<p>The whole “Study in Japan” thingy is now pretty much in doomed shape, after which there’s no way for it to progress whatsoever, others(mainly my “relatives” viewed me as “SELFISH” and “NOT CARING ABOUT PARENTS’ FINANCIAL SITUATION” and claimed that I didn’t see the fact that they do a lot of things thinking of me which I largely disagreed, and I would explain that they never went through a proper negociation with me and now we’re here, and they also stands firmly with my parents quote all of them knew when thet let me out and I will never be back, which is true, strikingly true) reckoned that It will be impossible for me in this state to live alone at all.<br />
The last point of which I agree with the most, at my current mental state, it will be impossible for me to achieve anything let alone something that require significant risk, but let me reminds them that the current state of which I am in, were largely caused by my parents, their miscommunication, their unwillingness of proper communication, the unwillingness of properly look at my actual thoughts with a straight eye, and now for anything I further suggests, they either rejected it or just rejected it and push the whole thing onto me to decide which the only thing on the todo list is to recall it.<br />
Which to me, tbh with you is no fun, really no fun, like I don’t know why I am still alive tho?  Why didn’t I kill myself already 10 odd years ago when I’ve decided to jump down the elementry school bldg. for some silly(albeit tbh not so silly) shit.  Why hadn’t I done it 7yrs ago when I got all the shit around me messed up, why I hadn’t done it 5yrs ago when I was at the edge ready to jump?<br />
And I keep on living till now where I am in a outcome that I knew it was coming in the past decade, now I am in it, deadlocked, looped, you know how While True works right, thats where I am in, and sure, I am planning a proper suicide with 100% success rate when executed but the day is on the way and the only question left is how long or how many more chances I want to give to this miserable live I am currently living which I knew that is not bad, I knew, but the truth of I could’ve gone a much much much better way if not for some silliest issues and silliest decicions made by my stubborn parents that thought they knew which is the best for me(which they didn’t) and which plan should they route for me(which they never thought it for more than a second).<br />
I am now in this terrible state where It just never gonna be good, this is the end, just how much longer I am willing to cope with this bullshit, and every couple of days I went into a loop where I believed things could got better or things is done time to go type of loop, endless.<br />
And I really must’ve said that I was furious when I heard of that my mom probably didn’t really care when I was getting into troubles, and now everyone believe its all my faults, and I was really furious about the fact that no one, absolutely no one, paid any attentions to me till I finally did something others never done before, even in my own fucking family, and they attack me for it, they create terrible stereotype for me based on that, e.g. the only reason I use a computer is when I game, like who the fuck you guys think you are, and who the fuck you guys really met with me during the year anyway, how many you guys know about me anyway, credit to my uncle(this time my mom’s younger bro) and his son(for now), that actually sat down, listen to me and my thoughts and let me actually explain what I am using (a clockworkpi uConsole), any explain why they’re interesting on it and what types of connections caused them to ask me about it(turns out his son in his 12, knew what Debian is and how to use a computer and I was like heck yeah you should go and continue down the road) which I am thankful of.<br />
Some might be asking, did your mom change for the slightest after all those shoutouts? I might say yes, but not for now, like I don’t really think she will change, and she was probably just going to escape from all of this and like nothing will change like the good old times.<br />
But anyway the only thing I wanted to say is that, a decision has been made, I will probably give two more quarters worth of chance to myself, and I would have myself kill, in my own hands, out of my own will, in a quiet day that nobody is going to know about place, to end all this.<br />
Which 2004.04.24 -&gt; Sometime in late-Q1/early-Q2 2026.<br />
I hope I could become a ghost that no one could notice and spying on anyone that have a good life for my own pleasure and I like to watch.</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much entered a fully block-out dead end and I don't want that.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">It caught me off guard again, this time with a far worst timing.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/08/bipolar-caught-me-off-guard.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It caught me off guard again, this time with a far worst timing." /><published>2026-02-08T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-02-08T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/02/08/bipolar-caught-me-off-guard</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/02/08/bipolar-caught-me-off-guard.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="howdy-somehow-back">Howdy, somehow back.</h1>
<p>I am kinda back after at least 4 days worth of extreme depressive period, with every single day more suffering than the days before it.<br />
You woked up late everyday even after full 12hrs of sleep that even me being someone who loves to sleep(i guess) starts to dislike this fact, when you’re asleep, all the nightmares are chasing you on your ass, 12hrs(maybe 8hr dreaming) worth of shit show chasing you on your back sure wasn’t something you would love to do.<br />
But you simply can’t get rid of it, your body simply drag you back down continue sleeping for no reason, I guess it’s not just about pills this time.<br />
My mom caught the worst timing in all of this yet, she tried to see how I am doing right in the middle of a transitional period(which my brain is on it’s way to tranform itself into depressive mode from a mixed/manic mode which I did a lot a thing for fun.)<br />
I simply just shit out a tons of fact that I simply didn’t enjoy all those playing card moment she gave me and all those single option choices she gave me and the fact that she never really stood up for me when I am the most in need.<br />
I mean, I did put all that down a few years ago and I am simply telling her the fact, and which somehow broke her and I am sorry about that but I don’t have time for that as well since I am starting to tearing all apart as well.<br />
And oh btw, the whole thing about “How happy you was in the Manic Period, how suffer you will be in the Depressive Period” is true I guess, I am now taking Lithiums and stuff like that regulary according to the prescription and after I told my doc about this she said we really needs to get that manic heat a bit down other wise I might get myself killed if Depressive hit.  Which I almost did yesterday.  I’ve already chosen a method for that.</p>
<h1 id="so-where-was-i-again-before-all-this">So… Where was I again, before all this</h1>
<p>I was messing with my GK-2A recepetion setup, and my receipt printer right before all those hit, and Idk maybe some other shit I forgot about.<br />
I did manage to set it up, but some how the long distance won’t do the trick, I guess I will move it back to the old house I reckon, after Lunar New Year I think.<br />
And my receipt printer stuff is running fine for now, printing news every 6 hrs for me to read. Yes I actually read news.</p>
<h1 id="next">Next?</h1>
<p>Idk I forgot/don’t want to take Concerta today so I am a bit hairy now and needs to sort things out, maybe I will just have some simple stuff sort out like replacing the screen protectors and dealing with miniDLAN/UPnP media server and watch some more YouTube and more Mangas for sure.<br />
And my somehow broken uConsole case’s 3D-printed replacement is going to arrive sometime tonight, and I guess that right-wing populist will win that snap election, ofc I hope she won’t but according to the numbers its… most likly the case.</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[And I am drafting my own "My Final Anwser to Life".]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I made something to monitor my Raspberry Pi 3 at home.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/27/simp-rpi-ups-mon.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I made something to monitor my Raspberry Pi 3 at home." /><published>2026-01-27T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-27T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/01/27/simp-rpi-ups-mon</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/27/simp-rpi-ups-mon.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="context">Context</h1>
<p>So I had this little Raspberry Pi 3 sitting around which I bought back in 2016.<br />
Yes I am still using it, why not?<br />
So recently I decided to let it run something instead of biting dust at home I installed DietPi on it and use it as a real server for some thing that I would actually use everyday, being slow is okay too, it’s fun innit?<br />
Anyway, in order to see how bad CSG is doing here I’ve decided to attach a <a href="https://github.com/linshuqin329/UPS-18650">mini UPS</a> to it, which pretty much is a block that sits underneath your Pi with two 18650 batteries connected to a <a href="https://www.analog.com/media/en/technical-documentation/data-sheets/MAX17040-MAX17041.pdf">MAX17041</a>.<br />
And what it brings is some I2C connection to my Pi for some stats to read, and with that plus A HUGE MERGER OF MY OTHER THREE PREVIOUS PROJECTS with something more blended in it, I’ve created:<br />
<a href="https://gist.github.com/theskanthunt42/02de49d7190eb4a0a867d66c2e532e10">SimpUPSMon</a> - <em>Some readings from my Raspberry Pi and it’s “UPS”</em>(sic)<br />
Which read some status from the Pi, some status from your browser, and <em>bang</em>！<br />
Oh and I hand wrote a basic HTTP server for this, just becauz I am lazy… so I just grab socket and do some rough TCP send thing… and called it a server.</p>
<h1 id="tldr">TL;DR</h1>
<p>Go see for yourself at(and your IP address + headers): <a href="https://front.the42.info/rpimon">SimpUPSMonSample</a></p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><category term="projects" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[And you could have a peek at it as well! Yes I am still using the OG Raspberry Pi 3b]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">No Place Is My Home.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/22/no-place-is-my-home.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Place Is My Home." /><published>2026-01-22T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-22T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/01/22/no-place-is-my-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/22/no-place-is-my-home.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="pov-youre-the-only-one-at-home-who-speaks-english-fluently-and-would-fact-check-all-the-things-youve-read-on-the-internet-and-dont-doom-scrolling-on-douyinweixins-brainwash-content-all-the-time">POV: You’re the only one at home who speaks English fluently and would fact-check all the things you’ve read on the internet and don’t doom-scrolling on Douyin/WeiXin’s brainwash content all the time.</h1>

<p>What I am dealing with every single day: 
<img src="/assets/imgs/shit-place.png" alt="Chat this is real." /></p>

<p>No Place is My Home really.</p>

<p>But whatever, I will just stop here, it’s not like any of you could really understand or relate to any of this anyway, you all frickin’ assholes.</p>

<p>Yeah, I am weak, not good enough, and I don’t have the dedications to work my way up in this situation.<br />
I am lazy yeah sure.</p>

<p>Fuck all of you.</p>

<p>Me irl(Except the looks of this cutie):</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">exams <a href="https://t.co/mH3tUIQTHL">pic.twitter.com/mH3tUIQTHL</a></p>&mdash; ✩ riku (@thecutemizuki) <a href="https://twitter.com/thecutemizuki/status/2014582785701208553?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 23, 2026</a></blockquote>
<script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<p>Gotta take more pills tonight huh.</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really can't relate to anyone, or rely on anyone, or feel at home when at home, I hate everyone, myself included.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I just hate all of you assholes bragging in front of me about your winner life’s flaw.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/18/me-at-my-peak.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I just hate all of you assholes bragging in front of me about your winner life’s flaw." /><published>2026-01-18T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-18T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/01/18/me-at-my-peak</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/18/me-at-my-peak.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/imgs/ky01.png" alt="You" /></p>

<p>It’s like… I don’t know if you guys are doing it on purpose, or just you are terribly bad at <em>“空気読め”</em><br />
But can you guys just STOP MENTIONING HOW BAD YOU LIVE OR HOW TERRIBLE A DECISION YOU’VE MADE when it’s OBIVIOUS THAT NO MATTER HOW “BAD” YOU LIVE, YOU STILL GOT A FAR FUCKING SUPERIOR LIFE THAN ME.</p>

<p>Just stop it and get some rest, really.<br />
Like, your mis-step or failure is like you messed up a single note so you didn’t win that whatever fucking international piano contests’(which your parent had it all arrange for you, and there wasn’t really much effort you need, just 2 years worth of afternoon class with a private teacher every Friday after you done with your private fucking school or sth) first prize and you can’t go to sleep all night when you was like 7yo.<br />
Or your pain is you didn’t get that praise from some specific teacher back in your “painful-youth” at an  international school or whatever.</p>

<p>I simply, don’t gives a fucking shit about it, nor is it some shit I could really fucking relates to, FULL FUCKING STOP.</p>

<p>Let’s make it clear, I am not poor or rich, simply a fucking college student in a middle-lower income working class family, and this is my limit, alright? Ofc, I knew there’s some improvements that COULD’VE BEEN MADE BACK IN THOSE DAYS BUT THATS HOW THIS WORLD WORKS!<br />
I went to public schools, most of my life(sometimes I went to private schools that it’s only purpose is to rip my wallet off but is the only way I could get a Bachelor degree), I don’t have rich fucking parents to help me with my shit, I learnt all this crap on my fucking own, in my fucking own free time, 50/50 on my fucking own free will/or being forced to. In order to talk to you bunch of fucking motherfucking mosquitoes that only knows how to suck on others suffering in a fucking greenhouse.</p>

<p>Just fucking stop, and don’t pretend you could relate with lower class(than you)’s miserable life.<br />
It’s GROSS!</p>

<p><strong>FUCK YOU.</strong></p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could you guys just shut up? It's quite noisy. Go circle jerk with your conterparts already.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Music of the Week 03 (Jan.12 - Jan.18, 2025)</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/motw/2603.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music of the Week 03 (Jan.12 - Jan.18, 2025)" /><published>2026-01-17T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-17T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/motw/motw-ch-02</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/motw/2603.html"><![CDATA[<p>At least I remember this week.<br />
Been messing with that exam week shit and watching Pluribus(Frankly it’s quite good! Go watch on Apple TV now!)<br />
So here we go…</p>

<p>Video rec.<br />
Finder - yoshinaoよしながき</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Fq7gZsTkas0?si=O5AyaBhAU8WHmOyy" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">Finder - yoshinaoよしながき</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>Yes, that Finder™ by Apple 1983-2026, kinda cool innit?
It’s the remake of “desktop” by the same author which came out in 2004: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wD4Mz-pY9oA</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<p>It’s been a busy(and sleepy) week so I don’t have that many time circle through my Apple Music playlist.<br />
I just repeat all those tracks I’ve recommended in the last <em>“issuse”</em> of MotW, but there are some stand-outs still.</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/zccBQLkVC0g?si=y6wv2PIpvAtarN-G" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">Simple cult classic by ZUN</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>Nothing to say, I have listened to this since my childhood… Sorry I am a weeb.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Wait what had I done this week, oh I’ve watched Pluribus on Apple TV, great show by the amazing Vince Gilligan crew again!</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Okay not much to say really… just stay tune for more… I’ve been asleep most of the time since went back home.</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music I looped on Wk 3 2026]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I am really into the whole “Why human sucks and why did they do that?” studies stuff, but I simply not smart enough for that, and always lacking motivations.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/11/lack-of-motivation-again.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I am really into the whole “Why human sucks and why did they do that?” studies stuff, but I simply not smart enough for that, and always lacking motivations." /><published>2026-01-11T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-11T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/01/11/lack-of-motivation-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/11/lack-of-motivation-again.html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="tldr">TL;DR</h2>

<p>I ain’t smart enough to not be an normie, I’ve already fully recognized it.<br />
Albeit I hate to be an normie.<br />
But I simply can’t.<br />
I don’t have the money, the ability to earn the money, and all the relationships to help me start to get some money or help to not be a normie.<br />
I am done.<br />
I mean, my life now is pretty much not worth living and I would want to end it.<br />
I hate all those rich bastard whom grew up and lived in a greenhouse and still failed to acknowledge that and claim their own “unfortunate” to others who grew up with a much worse situation.<br />
My problems were simple, my family tends to do bad choices at a bad time, simply out of silly believes and only hope things to be in their control, but not actually choose it because it’s beneficiary to the actual problem.<br />
And my own problem is that I am a coward. Afraid to speak up after all those shit…<br />
My family didn’t help me when I was being bullied, instead they sided with the bullies, and pointing fingers at me, and only after so many years the only <em>“apology”</em> I’ve got was “Oh I am sorry for that.” and nothing else.<br />
Meanwhile on the internet, the only place I thought I could rely and hide, now is turning it’s back on me.<br />
Rich assholes all around, they simply can’t even understand some basic shit going on in the society, are they totally a bad person? Probably not. But because of those misunderstanding they tends to be the bully.<br />
They just got better family, better parents who actually wants to help, and better financial background, and even for those “not all that rich” they got families that actually care. But not me.<br />
After all this, I always asked myself, do I still believe in the whole: “Hey I want to do something interesting or I live my own life.” project? With all this? I guess I haven’t totally give up on it yet, but mostly there.<br />
And let’s say this, uh… I’ve decided in my late 10s that I would just go Kill MySelf when I fully acknowledge that I can do nothing to achieve any of that.<br />
And on that behalf, let’s talk about something you guys hate or afraid to talks about, those mental health pills, actually really extend my life for some years, I could’ve already killed myself years ago. I reached sort of a mostly stable state instead of looking at the road crossing with car running through it everyday and think should I jump or cry in my futons everyday. No I actually starts to achieve something.  Really just stop asking me to stop taking pills, I tried, but nope that just how broken my brain is, and oh you might say “You wasn’t like that before you took those pills.”, bullshit, like what you have a cancer and you could no longer bear with it and you go through the therapy and take pills and take more care of yourself is a crime now? Like I was on the edge, did you guys helped me back then anyway? Anyone notice? Anyone please? Tons of garbage.<br />
So anyway, yeah sure when I see no chance in live the lifes I want to live in I would just end it, it’s been too much of a painful journey by this point.<br />
Just too many trauma and I am simply broken at this point, I just wants to be here for a bit longer.<br />
Yes, it’s painful to live, but for someone who actually been kicked out from hospital when seeking for help in physical issues by doctors and got shout at, and many simillar experiences as well, I just really hate to trust anyone anymore.<br />
I just love to mask myself, like it’s not even within my control. And I love to stay alone in order to back to normal again.</p>

<p>Alright I’ve talked too much, no one is gonna to read other than me anyway.<br />
Sometime just wondering will some of you attend my funeral or something lol, what would you think when I die, will you be unhappy or you just simply don’t care lol<br />
Just have my remainings (rust) somewhere in Japan’s ocean or lake or sth, that’s a beautiful place.<br />
But no worry, It won’t be now, I just want to stick a bit longer, and choosing a method to die that did not hurt that much or looks good is hard. And no one will care anyway.
I hate when ppl pretending they actually cared about others death.<br />
Why was I being born in the first place?<br />
My other shell just mask me inside it too well.</p>

<p>To those reading it with a LLM summarizer: I won’t rebuild, it’s pretty much the end of the show, shut the fuck up and fuck you all lazy ass.</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd love to sleep all day but thats boring but I would just stare at the blank screen all day if I forced me awake.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I know I am weird.</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/09/i-am-a-weirdo.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I know I am weird." /><published>2026-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/2026/01/09/i-am-a-weirdo</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/2026/01/09/i-am-a-weirdo.html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes sure I know, and I metioned it here alot, but the fact is, I am weird.</p>

<p>It’s not like I want to be proud of it or sth, oh btw, like, a lot of the weird ppl like to talk about their weirdness but they are all successful dudes and I am not so I won’t.<br />
Let’s all make it clear:</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>It is painful to live for being weird.<br />
You’re weird? Won’t have much friends, even you have any. And you will be prone to Ijime or Bullying.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Like at least for me I masked and learnt how to masked myself really hard, in order to keep me safe and won’t be hated by others.  Heck, my mom and some at her age used to say things like “You are really good at getting along with people!” or “Wow <strong>[MISGENDER MESS]</strong> really knows how to keep up with the others in an new enviornment! Amazing!”.<br />
Hey guys… it’s hard… and it’s painful in the process, and I have to act like I am normal all the time and with all those weird thing in my mind, which I have to always look at how others did it cautiously and tring to understand why they have to think like that, it’s so damn fucking hard. And in the end of course I wouldn’t understand them at all or sth, and sometimes if I walked too closely with others they will just got angry with me and be like “Why the fuck you can’t understand all this, do something!”(but do what really? What should I do when others angry with me, ACK my fault and apologize? I did but they didn’t accept it at all). And the end results was like either they forgive about me on this and understand I can’t do things like a normal one or I just walked away with no more connections with them(ofc most of the time they will be back after a few years or months but… I am sorry…)<br />
You know I used to thought “Hey I know I am a bit weird but others are the same they just masked it perfectly or sth” but turns out thats not the truth anyway.<br />
Speaking of which, I can’t really understand most of your feelings like… I can’t even discribe it but just so weird you guys, like why the fuck a lot of you just suddenly wants to date with a random (I don’t really know if that’s beauty or not) classmates that you just know about, for a bit, and you guys don’t really talk much anyway, why? That’s straight out lewd and disgustings but from my experience as a <strong>[OMG I HATE THIS GENDER THING]</strong> thats the norm…?  And I am the one thats being weird???</p>

<p>Besides, there are also alot of things I can’t understand, like I only use English medium to gather most of the informations like news or sometimes in Japanese, and I wrote my blogs in English, and I just watch a tons of videos on YouTube thats also in English, but it seems like that it’s a tall order for most of other guys…? at least for those around me.<br />
Like they love to talk about huge effort into learning or acquiring English as a second language, and from what I can tell yes they did, and they really seems desperate on topics like this. But when I said, hey you could try my way, watch, listen and use everyday, and just read read read and read, soon you will have a huge improvements, I did that for more than 10 years now and I don’t really go to some places thats speaks English.  But they were all like “yeah sure, but I simply can’t understand what they’re talking about.”  And oh my god I told them that “I don’t understand at first as well, but I just somehow learn it in this way and I just slowly started to understand what they were talking about like a baby growing up learning languages, and those Vids I picked are sth I am interested in anyway.”<br />
They said okay and went back and after that they still complains about they can’t understand English and oh boy what I saw just someone greedily doomscrolling on their phone with those fucking boring and “made to be funny but not actually funny” shit shorts.  And at that moment I realized that they’re doommed…</p>

<p>Speaking of Shorts(or <em>“TikToks”</em>), I don’t love those things… everysingle time when I accidentally got trolled into a YouTube shorts or something that was only posted on shorts I just have my brain immediately spills DANGER all over and just tell me to be aware, don’t scroll.  And I think I don’t really prefer those short vids… no context, not all that effort really, and not worth my time… and there are endless shorts waiting for you.<br />
But on the other hand, I love scrolling Twitter…? But most of my feeds are illustrations or interesting Japanese posts, albeit my “love” really depends if I am in the mood or not.  Oh and theres the YouTube thing… Yeah I love documentary on tech or some demostration vids(so I don’t need to buy them). And I love to rewatch all the things I’ve watch before and wait for bots to find something I might like for me.</p>

<p>Alright anyway, Idk, I am a bit bored just so I have a lot of things to say, and my social battery went out of batts this week so I don’t feel like go to SNS and have a deep chat with friends or sth, I needs to be alone, to be happy or like to talk with others again.  If some of you actually read this far down here, I apologize for all those “Not online in 10hrs moment…” I just simply don’t want to, my brain is trying to stop me from doing it, I an tired. I am sorry…</p>

<p>And there’s the other thing I felt I am pretty weird in, when I was still a… uuh… normal students that not yet needed to take mental health pills, I used to admire those who does, like they had the freedom to take it, normal pals will be afraid of them since they don’t want to accidentally hurt them for whatever reason(to those normal pals, thank you, but all of you are cowards afraid of deaths).  But now after I’ve got most part of my brain messed up and take tons a pill a day to keep on track with my life I started thinking: This shouldn’t be like this, albeit again, it does feel a bit more free, my parents are more careful towards my feelings and my thoughts, they will no longer force me or surveillance me 24*7(I will talk about more on this later, but one question for you: have you ever been required by your parents to let them check the status of your pee or the status of your shit after you take a dump in toliet? Go figure. Tho I don’t really hate them that much now, I reckon they just did it like thet’re crazy…) but is that it…? With the cost of they still not really want me to study abroad or even allowing me to live on my own… Really? Yeah gotta admit I have regrets on that, but my mental health at that point could no longer suffer so…</p>

<p>Ah, and there’s good old Shenzhen Museme debacle, I won’t talk about it as well, although I am in pretty stable mental states now but won’t ever try. I no longer have nightmares related to it in recent years (at least after 2023 when I realized hey I was just in the wrong place with a bunch of assholes, oh fuck I should stop talking about this, I started to remember what happened… FULL STOP).</p>

<p>So hey, how’s your first full week in 2026 been? whoa time flies so fast, tho I some how feeling 2025 felt like an eternal but also not… weird…</p>

<p>I still needs to figure out something in the next few days:</p>
<ul>
  <li>iPod Touch or Nokia Touchscreens
    <ul>
      <li>if iPod touch that really ain’t all that much fun, but hey at least it got iOS 15… wait that’s a bit too old as well.</li>
      <li>if Nokia, Symbian or MeeGo/Maemo?
        <ul>
          <li>if Symbian, N8 or 808 Pureview?(I prefer the latter tbh, but N8 was my dream machine when I was a kid!)</li>
          <li>if MeeGo/Maemo, N9 or N900…? both seems fun</li>
        </ul>
      </li>
      <li>Only reason that I ain’t buying yet: all of them HSDPA at best… and 3G was pretty much long gone here</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Should I gave it a chance and study that subject I have no idea on for the finals? Or just praise for the best, like I did when dealing with French, wait no I actuallt spent some time on it.</li>
  <li>The whole Concerta situation… should I take it tmr(weekends) to write more shit or read more stuff online in front of my PC or just not take anything and go grab some sleep for a boring whole day?</li>
</ul>

<p>Too messed up, I am way too messed up… But whatever…<br />
I reckon I should figure out how to install old OSX on my modern VM lol.<br />
Anyway, see ya next post.</p>

<p>Oh wait, heres some music I really enjoyed today(again, by namitape):</p>
<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/H8RccLmo0k4?si=lxracICu5lIWk7xR" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">幽体ランドセル - Namitape</iframe>

<p>So, see ya tmr, I guess. Gotta hit YouTube really quick till dinner lol</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="thoughts" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rage typing as the first(out of two) exam week ends.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Music of the Week 02 (Jan.5 - Jan.11, 2025)</title><link href="https://front.the42.info/motw/2602.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music of the Week 02 (Jan.5 - Jan.11, 2025)" /><published>2026-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2026-01-09T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://front.the42.info/motw/motw-ch-01</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://front.the42.info/motw/2602.html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a pilot, let’s all hope I could continue updating it.</p>

<iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *;" frameborder="0" height="150" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;background:transparent;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/album/more-sq-final-fantasy-vi-searching-for-friends/1838355833?i=1838355891">More SQ: FINAL FANTASY VI Searching for friends - Special Others</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>A remix/jazzy version of that famous(and great) World Map BGM from the OG Final Fantasy VI</p>
</blockquote>

<p>OG fyi:</p>

<iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *;" frameborder="0" height="150" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;background:transparent;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/album/searching-for-friends/62447175?i=62447059">Searching for Friends - Nobuo Uematsu</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>The best World Map OST I’ve ever heard in an JRPG, albeit a post-collapse one.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Speaking of Final Fantasy VI, sure gonna fiddle with boring commutes with the amazing:</p>

<iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *;" frameborder="0" height="150" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;background:transparent;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/album/dancing-mad/62447175?i=62447131">Dancing Mad - Nobuo Uematsu</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>The final boss fight battle BGM, 17 mins long, amazingly composed and crazy.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<iframe allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *;" frameborder="0" height="150" style="width:100%;max-width:660px;overflow:hidden;background:transparent;" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" src="https://embed.music.apple.com/us/album/eien-no-shunmu/1580541476?i=1580541484">永遠の春夢 - ZUN</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>What can I say? Simply amazing. Although I reckon the name will cause a bit of confusion when introducing it to new comers… especially those know how to read kanji.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<p>Speaking of which:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>zun 的小号吹得好~ zun 的小号吹得好~ zun 的小号吹的真好呐~~ zun 的小号吹得真好~~</p>
</blockquote>

<p>by Troubadour Ggmz on <a href="https://thbwiki.cc/%E6%B0%B8%E8%BF%9C%E7%9A%84%E6%98%A5%E6%A2%A6">THBWiki</a></p>

<p>Tranlation(in accurate but you get the gist of it): “This is the ZUNPet where and how, this the ZUNPet ri-ight now, ZUN really knows how to, to put the ZUNPet in the right placeeeeeeeee.”</p>

<p><br /></p>

<p><em>Read this with</em> 永遠の春夢 <em>starting at 1:00</em></p>

<p><br /></p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/H8RccLmo0k4?si=lL948hcV2a_fROhb" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">幽体ランドセル - namitape</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>Simply amazing, part of the (my personal) PEAK namitape collection.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><br /></p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Us5033N1t8o?si=nes4CqBHhtO_EkKi" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="">やる気がない feat. 歌愛ユキ - namitape</iframe>

<blockquote>
  <p>My whole week be like. <a href="/2026/01/08/not-motivated.html">I AM NOT MOTIVATED</a></p>
</blockquote>

<p>Lght, that sums up for this week, you could also follows me on <a href="https://music.apple.com/profile/the42game">Apple Music</a> lol</p>]]></content><author><name>the42game</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music I looped on Wk 2 2026]]></summary></entry></feed>